<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>backpacking on Peaks and Plains</title>
    <link>https://blog.kwen.ca/tags/backpacking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in backpacking on Peaks and Plains</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 12:51:40 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.kwen.ca/tags/backpacking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Skoki Loop</title>
      <link>https://blog.kwen.ca/posts/skoki-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 12:51:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kwen.ca/posts/skoki-loop/</guid>
      <description>The Lake Louise/Skoki area in fall is to die for. This was a fun and laid back weekend trip in almost-optimal conditions.
Date: 2020-09-11 to 2020-09-13
Location: Banff National Park
Friends: Chris, Kat, Nick, Mel, John, Eric
Day 1 - Fish Creek trailhead to Hidden Lake campground Half of us headed out fairly late in the afternoon and got to camp just in time to set up our tent before the sun went down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockwall</title>
      <link>https://blog.kwen.ca/posts/rockwall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 23:23:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kwen.ca/posts/rockwall/</guid>
      <description>Rockwall Trail is my new favourite backpacking trip. There was so much to love about this hike: stupendous views every day, great company, sunny and warm weather, wonderful campgrounds, endless fields of wildflowers, epic towering mountains and glaciers, and abundant streams, rivers, creeks, and waterfalls. On a personal note, the lack of knee pain (unlike last year) made the hike even more enjoyable.
My friends and I completed the hike North to South in three nights staying at Helmet Falls, Tumbling Creek, and Floe Lake, which I think was ideal in terms of pacing and daily distance/elevation gain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skyline Trail</title>
      <link>https://blog.kwen.ca/posts/skyline-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 23:08:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kwen.ca/posts/skyline-trail/</guid>
      <description>Skyline was probably the hike that first led me to backpacking. I discovered it two years ago in 2016&amp;frasl;17 and since then, was obsessed with the thought of hiking it. Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve actually done it, it feels strange! The weather was good, the views were great, the company was awesome, I packed my gear really well (light), the only thing that wassn&amp;rsquo;t good were my knees.
Date: 2019-08-03 to 2019-08-05</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Egypt Lake</title>
      <link>https://blog.kwen.ca/posts/egypt-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 22:49:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kwen.ca/posts/egypt-lake/</guid>
      <description>Redemption for the attempt last year! Lots of friends, lots of fun.
Date: 2019-06-29 to 2019-07-01
Location: Banff
Friends: Chris, Kat, Nick, Ivan, Eric, Tess, Evan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healy Pass</title>
      <link>https://blog.kwen.ca/posts/healy-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kwen.ca/posts/healy-pass/</guid>
      <description>That day, a valiant attempt was made to backpack to Egypt Lake. It was also probably the most miserable, soggy, muddy, and nasty walk I&amp;rsquo;ve ever had. An entire day of trudging up small rivers in the chilly gloom. By the time we made it to the pass, the sunlight and gorgeous sights cheered us up, but we decided to head back since everyone&amp;rsquo;s shoes were wet at that point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake Minnewanka and Aylmer Peak</title>
      <link>https://blog.kwen.ca/posts/lake-minnewanka-and-aylmer-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 20:48:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kwen.ca/posts/lake-minnewanka-and-aylmer-peak/</guid>
      <description>The First backpacking trip! There were some bear scares, and some other scares too, and I had no idea what I was doing most of the time. Still a wonderful weekend with many good memories made. I never actually made it up Mount Aylmer - the summit photos where taken by Chris.
Date: 2018-08-04 to 2018-08-06
Location: Banff
Friends: Chris, Nick, Spencer, Lucy
Trailhead: Lake Minnewanka parking lot</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>