<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hiking on Peaks and Plains</title>
    <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/tags/hiking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hiking on Peaks and Plains</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 23:19:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://adventures.kwen.ca/tags/hiking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ha Ling Peak III</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/ha-ling-peak-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 23:19:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/ha-ling-peak-iii/</guid>
      <description>Sunrise hikes are a hard sell but they are a bit easier during the winter when you can wake up a bit later. Jonathan, Chris, and I were blessed with a stunning sunrise today, which made the 4 am wake up worth it.
Date: 2020-11-22
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Chris, Jonathan
We started hiking in the dark at 6 am and made it to the summit just before sunrise. I overestimated my ability to bound up the last grind at the end and found myself huffing and puffing my way up there, as usual!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pocaterra Ridge</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/pocaterra-ridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 22:11:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/pocaterra-ridge/</guid>
      <description>Kat and I attempted the ever-popular Pocaterra Ridge hike for the first time on Thanksgiving weekend. We didn&amp;rsquo;t arrive particularly early but we still somehow ended up being the first ones there. With the fresh snow that had fallen, we had to break trail for most of the hike.
It was definitely challenging to navigate terrain for a hike we&amp;rsquo;d never done before, but we eventually made our way to the summit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen Lake</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/helen-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/helen-lake/</guid>
      <description>A classic fall-hike-turned-winter-then-back-to-fall-again with the folks. The original plan was to do Larch Valley/Eiffel Peak/Sentinel Pass but we didn&amp;rsquo;t head out early enough to get a spot in the parking lot. Helen Lake/Cirque Peak was our backup and it turned out to be a delightful hike! The brief snow storm we encountered was magical rather than scary, and resulted in some stunning &amp;ldquo;winter&amp;rdquo; views. We didn&amp;rsquo;t end up attempting Cirque Peak since it was too snowy and it was getting late in the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skoki Loop</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/skoki-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 12:51:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/skoki-loop/</guid>
      <description>The Lake Louise/Skoki area in fall is to die for. This was a fun and laid back weekend trip in almost-optimal conditions.
Date: 2020-09-11 to 2020-09-13
Location: Banff National Park
Friends: Chris, Kat, Nick, Mel, John, Eric
Day 1 - Fish Creek trailhead to Hidden Lake campground Half of us headed out fairly late in the afternoon and got to camp just in time to set up our tent before the sun went down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burstall Pass</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/burstall-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 17:53:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/burstall-pass/</guid>
      <description>A beautiful, bluebird day! Some fun stream crossings and the best part: there weren&amp;rsquo;t many people on this hike. Next time, I would love to go a bit further and make it to Leman Lake.
Date: 2020-08-16
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Mom and dad</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Beehive</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/big-beehive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 23:26:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/big-beehive/</guid>
      <description>It was a super busy day and we were only able to get parking due to a stroke of good luck. The goal was to hike to the plain of the six glaciers but we were distracted along the way and never made it there&amp;hellip;
Date: 2020-08-09
Location: Banff
Friends: The parents
Mount Rundle over Vermillion Lake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mount Bourgeau</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/mount-bourgeau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 23:25:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/mount-bourgeau/</guid>
      <description>What a summer this has been! Wonderful hikes, amazing weather, and so many great photos.
Mount Bourgeau (and Harvey Pass) might be my new favourite day hike. The approach was yet again very long and uneventful. After two hours, we arrived at Bourgeau Lake, which to me was a less awe-inspiring Rockbound Lake. Luckily, it was a short and easy climb past Bourgeau Lake to the spectacular Harvey Pass. Upon reaching the pass, I felt like I had arrived in some sort of paradise on earth: glacial lakes, lush green alpine meadows, fields of wildflowers, and crystal-clear streams, all surrounded by towering mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockwall</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/rockwall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 23:23:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/rockwall/</guid>
      <description>Rockwall Trail is my new favourite backpacking trip. There was so much to love about this hike: stupendous views every day, great company, sunny and warm weather, wonderful campgrounds, endless fields of wildflowers, epic towering mountains and glaciers, and abundant streams, rivers, creeks, and waterfalls. On a personal note, the lack of knee pain (unlike last year) made the hike even more enjoyable.
My friends and I completed the hike North to South in three nights staying at Helmet Falls, Tumbling Creek, and Floe Lake, which I think was ideal in terms of pacing and daily distance/elevation gain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nihahi Ridge</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/nihahi-ridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 23:46:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/nihahi-ridge/</guid>
      <description>Kat and I attempted Nihahi Ridge while Greg and Chris biked the Elbow loop. This turned out to be a great idea. We were also trying to take it easy the weekend before our big trip.
Nihahi Ridge as a hike has never excited me but it turned out to be fun, especially the super-steep and slippery slopes, and the hands-on parts near the summit. We did not quite make it to the South summit but it was a good challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockbound Lake</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/rockbound-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/rockbound-lake/</guid>
      <description>A very long forested approach, but the lake was quite nice, especially from up high. It was also surprisingly cold at the lake compared with the forest. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to come back and climb Castle Mountain.
Date: 2020-07-18
Location: Banff
Friends: Ingrid, Kat
The lake was constantly changing colours depending on the sunlight and clouds moving across the sky.
A hiking lesson I&amp;rsquo;ve learned: it&amp;rsquo;s always worth it to try getting above a lake if you can - the colours are so much better from above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mount Allan II</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/mount-allan-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/mount-allan-ii/</guid>
      <description>A hot and sunny day that wasn&amp;rsquo;t too unbearable due to the wind. The hike was decently busy and a great challenge. Got briefly lost during the scrambling part (again), but it was fun!
Date: 2020-07-11
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Kat, Robyn
There&amp;rsquo;s Pigeon from last weekend!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pigeon Mountain</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/pigeon-mountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/pigeon-mountain/</guid>
      <description>I was so impressed with this beautiful hike! Pigeon mountain is not too strenuous but still long and high enough to be a good workout. The views are amazing - both along the way and at the summit. The trail is just a straightforward stroll to the top and back down and the trailhead is only an hour away from Calgary.
Date: 2020-07-05
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Ingrid, Kat
The hike begins along a transmission line right-of-way for the first 5 kilometres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cox Hill via North Jumpingpound Ridge</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/cox-hill-via-jumpingpound/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/cox-hill-via-jumpingpound/</guid>
      <description>The hike We hiked this one-way from the north end of Jumpingpound Ridge to Cox Hill and down to the Dawson equestrian area. The rest of the family biked a big loop from the parking lot. The hike was a gentle hike up and down but I heard it was pretty strenuous to mountain bike. The wildflowers were still out in full bloom and my favourite part of the hike was the open meadow between Jumpingpound Ridge and Cox Hill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Lougheed</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/little-lougheed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/little-lougheed/</guid>
      <description>Another short and fun hike with a great view of Spray Lake. I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen so many people parked on the side of the road on the Smith-Dorrien - everyone seems to be itching to get out these days. The hike was busy but there was plenty of space for groups to pass each other.
Date: 2020-06-20
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Kat
The lower third of the hiking trail goes through pleasant green forest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>King Creek Ridge</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/king-creek-ridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 22:10:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/king-creek-ridge/</guid>
      <description>King Creek Ridge has an excellent effort-to-reward ratio, as can be seen from the photos. How lucky are Calgarians to see these views in the morning and still be home in time for lunch? The hike is very similar to Prairie Mountain in terms of length and elevation gain, but the views are out of the world for the amount of time you spend climbing. We ascended and descended via two different well-worn trails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumpingpound Summit</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/jumpingpound-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 22:02:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/jumpingpound-summit/</guid>
      <description>The shortest hike I&amp;rsquo;ve done in years and it still kicked my ass! It&amp;rsquo;s rough coming out of quarantine mode.
Date: 2020-06-06
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Katrin, Chris</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prairie Mountain II</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/prairie-mountain-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 23:46:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/prairie-mountain-ii/</guid>
      <description>One of the best feelings in the world is reaching a summit when you haven&amp;rsquo;t been outside in a while. The weather was nice and the rain at the trailhead turned into magical fluffy snowflakes a third of the way up. At the summit, any views were obstructed by fog. With the oppressive gloom pressing down around us, and the persistent drone of an airplane somewhere above, our time on the summit felt unsettling and eerie and somewhat post-apocalyptic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mount St. Piran</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/mount-st-piran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/mount-st-piran/</guid>
      <description>This was my attempt to squeeze in one last hike before the hiking season &amp;ldquo;officially&amp;rdquo; ended. There had been a lot of snowfall in parts of Kananaskis but barely any in Lake Louise. Asking around resulted in various conflicting reports of avalanche and winter conditions. We decided to head out to the Lake Louise area and check the conditions out for ourselves. There was probably a foot of snow at higher elevations, but everything was otherwise very hikeable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skyline Trail</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/skyline-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 23:08:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/skyline-trail/</guid>
      <description>Skyline was probably the hike that first led me to backpacking. I discovered it two years ago in 2016&amp;frasl;17 and since then, was obsessed with the thought of hiking it. Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve actually done it, it feels strange! The weather was good, the views were great, the company was awesome, I packed my gear really well (light), the only thing that wassn&amp;rsquo;t good were my knees.
Date: 2019-08-03 to 2019-08-05</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windtower</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/windtower/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 23:08:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/windtower/</guid>
      <description>Another &amp;ldquo;easy scramble&amp;rdquo; with high payoff. Nonstop views from the moment you get past treeline. Tried this hike last year and did not make it past West Wind Pass due to weather. Bit of easy scrambling/route finding after the pass. All trails eventually lead to the same place, and lots of people to follow if you get lost. Views of Spray Lake along the way are classic. All in all, my kind of hike!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mount Hoffman</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/mount-hoffman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 23:03:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/mount-hoffman/</guid>
      <description>Someone brought some steaks and cooked them in a cast iron skillet at the &amp;ldquo;summit&amp;rdquo;. It was that kind of hike.
Date: 2019-07-13
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: All the friends</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Egypt Lake</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/egypt-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 22:49:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/egypt-lake/</guid>
      <description>Redemption for the attempt last year! Lots of friends, lots of fun.
Date: 2019-06-29 to 2019-07-01
Location: Banff
Friends: Chris, Kat, Nick, Ivan, Eric, Tess, Evan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Peak</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/midnight-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 21:52:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/midnight-peak/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2019-06-22
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Kat, Devin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Coach Trail</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/old-coach-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/old-coach-trail/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2019-04-26
Location: Kootenay National Park
Friends: Tess, Michelle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sulphur Mountain</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/sulphur-mountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/sulphur-mountain/</guid>
      <description>It was icy going up. We took the gondola on the way down.
Date: 2018-11-03
Location: Banff
Friends: Ab, Chris</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healy Pass</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/healy-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/healy-pass/</guid>
      <description>That day, a valiant attempt was made to backpack to Egypt Lake. It was also probably the most miserable, soggy, muddy, and nasty walk I&amp;rsquo;ve ever had. An entire day of trudging up small rivers in the chilly gloom. By the time we made it to the pass, the sunlight and gorgeous sights cheered us up, but we decided to head back since everyone&amp;rsquo;s shoes were wet at that point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Larch Valley and Eiffel Peak</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/larch-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 00:17:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/larch-valley/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2018-09-15
Location: Banff
Distance: 14 km
Elevation gain: 600 m
Time: 7 h
Friends: Chris, Eric, Nick, Ken</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Picklejar Lakes</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/picklejar-lakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 10:16:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/picklejar-lakes/</guid>
      <description>A fun outing with friends. There are quite a few lakes at the end of the hike, and amazing colours during fall.
Date: 2018-09-08
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: A bunch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mount Allan</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/mount-allan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 10:16:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/mount-allan/</guid>
      <description>Mount Allan is long, strenuous, rewarding, not best of all, has no exposure. You get to hike to the top of Nakiska ski resort, then hike up even higher! This was a perfect day.
Date: 2018-09-01
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Ken, Jonathan, Ivan, Nick</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sparrowhawk Tarns</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/sparrowhawk-tarns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 10:16:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/sparrowhawk-tarns/</guid>
      <description>Between the gentle incline, pretty landscape, abundant fossils, and fields of whistling marmots, this was an enjoyable day hike. Unfortunately, the wildfires were going full force at the time.
Date: 2018-08-25
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Ab</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake Minnewanka and Aylmer Peak</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/lake-minnewanka-and-aylmer-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 20:48:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/lake-minnewanka-and-aylmer-peak/</guid>
      <description>The First backpacking trip! There were some bear scares, and some other scares too, and I had no idea what I was doing most of the time. Still a wonderful weekend with many good memories made. I never actually made it up Mount Aylmer - the summit photos where taken by Chris.
Date: 2018-08-04 to 2018-08-06
Location: Banff
Friends: Chris, Nick, Spencer, Lucy
Trailhead: Lake Minnewanka parking lot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barrier Lake Lookout</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/barrier-lake-lookout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 10:15:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/barrier-lake-lookout/</guid>
      <description>Also known as Prairie View Lookout. Also known as Yates Mountain. A short hike on a scorchingly hot day.
Date: 2018-07-28
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Ivan, Nick, Kristie, Yakov, Carl, Yaw</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upper Kananaskis Lake</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/upper-kananaskis-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 01:53:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/upper-kananaskis-lake/</guid>
      <description>Weekend camping trip with friends at Boulton Creek Campground. We walked part of the way around Upper Kananaskis Lake - always a beauty!
Date: 2018-07-20 to 2018-07-21
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Sonia, Lisa, Michelle, Tess, Annie, Alecia, Connie</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Table Mountain, Road trip through Castle and Waterton</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/table-mountain-castle-waterton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 01:46:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/table-mountain-castle-waterton/</guid>
      <description>Canada Day road trip through Castle and Waterton park.
Date: 2018-06-30 to 2018-07-02
Location: Castle Provincal Park, Waterton National Park
Friends: Chris, and a caravan along the way
Drive to Castle We started off with the most scenic drive down Highway 533, then Highway 22 - also known as Cowboy Trail. I don&amp;rsquo;t think this highway has ever disappointed me with its views.
Castle Falls was a gorgeous and quiet campground, filled with the rushing sound of water from the nearby Castle Falls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wasootch Ridge</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/wasootch-ridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 01:43:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/wasootch-ridge/</guid>
      <description>After walking down a riverbed for ten minutes, we realized that we were heading down the wrong trail and had to turn back to the parking lot. Despite the great weather and open views, this hike didn&amp;rsquo;t do it for me. Maybe it was the endless, unsatisfying ups and downs of the ridgewalk, or the unchanging views which got old after a few hours. We did not make it very far down the ridge before we turned back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ha Ling Peak II</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/ha-ling-peak-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 17:11:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/ha-ling-peak-ii/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2018-05-20
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Mom and dad</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rawson Lake</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/rawson-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 15:26:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/rawson-lake/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2018-01-15
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Dad, Luselle, Jemma</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Wind Pass</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/west-wind-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 16:48:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/west-wind-pass/</guid>
      <description>A Wind Tower attempt. We made it to the pass, took a look at the snow-covered slopes above us, and decided to turn back. It was a chilly day and the pass was indeed windy!
Date: 2017-10-21
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Chris</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galatea Creek Trail</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/galatea-creek-trail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 14:49:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/galatea-creek-trail/</guid>
      <description>Great conditions in late fall. The hike felt longer than it looked on paper. We were caught in a snow squall at the second Galatea Lake so we turned back and didn&amp;rsquo;t make it to the third one.
Date: 2017-10-08
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Mom and dad</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Powderface Ridge</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/powderface-ridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 14:49:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/powderface-ridge/</guid>
      <description>A relaxed outing on a lovely fall day.
Date: 2017-09-16
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Alecia, Lisa, Sonia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chester Lake</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/chester-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 14:49:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/chester-lake/</guid>
      <description>A quick and easy hike with friends. Larches abound in this area.
Date: 2017-09-10
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: All the friends</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yamnuska</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/yamnuska/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/yamnuska/</guid>
      <description>We ended up bushwacking down but it was still fun!
Date: 2017-09-04
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Chris, Sonia, Nic, Michelle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moose Mountain</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/moose-mountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 18:02:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/moose-mountain/</guid>
      <description>A casual hike right outside of Calgary. I’ve been wanting to hike Moose Mountain for a while now. It was a bluebird day and even though the annual Moose Mountain Trail Race was going on, we didn’t pass by many people – always a plus!
Date: 2017-08-26
Location: Kananaskis
Distance: 15 km
Elevation gain: 515 m
Time: 5 hours, including a one-hour lunch break
Friends: Jonathan, Michelle, Nic, Emily, Connor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ha Ling Peak and Miner’s Peak</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/ha-ling-peak-and-miners-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/ha-ling-peak-and-miners-peak/</guid>
      <description>Short and super-popular. Steep going up with some scrambling at the top.
Date: 2017-08-19
Location: Kananaskis
Distance: 7 km
Elevation gain: 740 m
Time: 4 h, including some long breaks
Friends: Mario, Chris
No photos from the initial ascent, which was on a well-marked trail through forest.
Shortly after clearing the treeline, it gets a lot rockier and steeper.
Miner’s Peak is right beside Ha Ling Peak.
All these people taking different routes to the summit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ptarmigan Cirque</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/ptarmigan-cirque/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/ptarmigan-cirque/</guid>
      <description>A short and popular trail that also happened to be really pretty. Drove an hour and a half to Highwood Pass, the highest paved pass in Canada. It was 30 degrees in Calgary but felt about 17 up in the cirque because of the high elevation.
Date: 2017-07-25
Location: Kananaskis
Distance: 6.5 km (started scrambling up Mount Rae)
Elevation gain: 300 m
Time: 2 hours (including long-ish breaks)
Friends: Chris, Mario</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South End of Mount Lawson</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/south-end-of-mount-lawson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/south-end-of-mount-lawson/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2017-07-02
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Mom and Dad</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prairie Mountain</title>
      <link>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/prairie-mountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 18:08:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventures.kwen.ca/posts/prairie-mountain/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2017-06-11
Location: Kananaskis
Friends: Chris, Mario, Julia</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>